

SHAH

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Graphic Design

Motion Graphic

Web Design

2D Animation

About me:

Experienced graphic designer with 11 years in the industry. Keenly interested in front-end development and UI design. Known for a strong work ethic, passion for learning, and a drive for excellence in competitive environments.

Name Muhammad Shahril Fadzlyn

Bin Baharin

Language Malay • Native

English • Basic

CONTACT

Mobile 016 - 9191 002

E-mail shahrilfadzlyn@gmail.com

Website shahrilfadzlyn.wix.com/

sfportfolio

Address 11, Jalan Wangsa 1/3,

Taman Wangsa Permai, 52200, Kuala Lumpur

REFERENCE

Name Mr. S S Loong

Position Manager of Prepress Dept.

Mobile 017 - 692 1538

Address UPA PRESS SDN. BHD.

Lot 8228, Batu 6½, Jalan Kuchai Lama 58200 Kuala Lumpur.



WORK EXPERIENCE

2017 - Present UPA Press Sdn. Bhd.

Graphic Designer (Freelance)

Locum Net Asia Sdn. Bhd **Graphic Designer** (Freelance)

Jawi Streetwear

Graphic Designer (Self-employed)

2017 - 2018 SF Motion Studio

2D Animator (Self-employed)

2014 - 2017 UPA Press Sdn. Bhd.

Graphic Designer (Permanent)

2013 - 2014 iProduksi

2D Animator (Freelance)

FNF Printing

Graphic Designer (Self-employed)

Vermilion Concept

Wedding Photographer (Self-employed)

2011 DotPerInchStudio

Graphic Designer (Internship)



EDUCATION

2011 - 2013 Ba (hons) Media Practice with Animation

Second Class Honours (Upper Division)

University of the West of England, United Kingdom

2008 - 2011 Diploma in Digital Media Design

CGPA 3.67

Kolej Kemahiran Tinggi MARA Rembau

2006 - 2007 **SPM; 1A, 3B, 2C, 2D, 1E** SMK Sri Tasik, Kuala Lumpur



ACHIEVEMENT

2015 Best Performance Award

UPA Press Sdn Bhd.

2014 Best Performance Award

UPA Press Sdn Bhd.

2010 **1st Place winner**, Graphic Design Technology,

Malaysia Skills Competition, 19th

Best Artwork Award, Digital Media, 5th Semester

Kolej Kemahiran Tinggi MARA Rembau

All Rounder Best Artwork Award

Kolej Kemahiran Tinggi MARA Rembau



TECHNICAL SKILLS

Adobe Suite

Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Flash/Animate, After Effects, Premiere & Audition

Microsoft Office Suite
Word, Excel & Powerpoint

Coding

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, VueJS

Other Software/App

Figma, VSCode, Canva, Capcut, ChatGPT 4



MUHAMMAD SHAHRIL FADZLYN BIN BAHARIN

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

WORK EXPERIENCE

Graphic Designer

UPA Press Sdn. Bhd. 2017 - Present (*Freelance*) 2014 - 2017 (*Permanent*)

- Responsible for designing table calendars and diaries for both domestic and international clients.
- Reviewing and correcting the format, color, and layout of artwork received from customers before printing.
- Maintaining consistent communication with customers until the artwork is finalized.
- Operating laser cutting and prepress printing machines to provide color proofs and mock-up samples for customers.
- Collaborated closely with the sales team, supervisors, and production manager on every project.
- Actively participated in the Research & Development team for our new products.
- Responsible for photographing our latest product lines.
- Shared knowledge and mentored junior graphic designers.
 Actively contributed to the design of our website.

Graphic Designer (Freelance)

Locum Net Asia Sdn. Bhd. | 2021 - Present

- · Responsible:
 - > Create corporate identity.
 - > Involved in creating UI and UX for our app.
 - > Create a video advertisement to showcase our app.
 - > Create marketing material.

Graphic Designer (Self-employed)

Jawi Streetwear | 2021 - 2022

- · Responsible:
 - > Create brand identity.
 - > Conduct product research & development.
 - Dealing with supplier.
 - > Create social media & website.
 - > Create content & marketing material.
 - > Capturing images of products.
 - > Entertain prospects and customers.

2D Animator (Self-employed) SF Motion Studio | 2017 - 2018

- Create 2D animation content on Facebook & Youtube.
- Provides 2D animation & graphic design service for international customer on Fiverr, a global online marketplace.

2D Animator (Freelance)

iProduksi | 2013 - 2014

- Responsible to develop concept art & producing 2 - 3 minutes of an animated music video for a campaign on TV3.
- Responsible to develop concept art & producing an animated pilot episode for our cartoon series.

Wedding photographer (Self-employed)

Vermilion Concept | 2013 - 2014

• Responsible to take pictures for a wedding ceremony.

Graphic Designer (Self-employed)

FNF Printing | 2013 - 2014

- Responsible:
 - > Create corporate identity.
 - > Create designs for bunting, banner, business card, T-shirt & logo our customer.